RG 169:007, Connecticut Forest and Park Association
Connecticut State Library
- Series 8. Publications, circa 1883-2011
  - Connecticut Walk Books, 1937-1984 (Box 15, Folder 18-27)
    - Connecticut Walk Book Fourteenth Edition. Publication number 36Q. East Hartford, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1984
  - Connecticut Walk Books, 1987-1997 (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
    - Connecticut Walk Book Fifteenth Edition. Publication number 36-R. Middletown, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1987
    - Connecticut Walk Book Sixteenth Edition. Publication number 36-S. Middletown, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1990
    - Connecticut Walk Book Seventeenth Edition. Publication number 36-T. Middlefield, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1993
    - Connecticut Walk Book Eighteenth Edition - 60th Anniversary Edition. Publication number 36-U. Middletown, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1997
  - Connecticut Wood Energy Kit - A guide for small commercial/industrial installation or conversion, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Woodlands, 1936-1969; 17 volumes (Box 23, Folder 1-17)
  - Connecticut Woodlands, 1970-1997; 14 volumes (Box 24, Folder 1-14)
  - Connecticut Woodlands, 1998-2011; 7 volumes (Box 25, Folder 1-7)
  - Lowdermilk, W. C. Conquest of the Land through 7,000 years. Agriculture Information Bulletin number 99. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Harper, Walter L. and Edwin D. Carpenter. Contemporary Ground Covers. Storrs, CT: Cooperative Extension Service, College of Agriculture, University of Connecticut, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Copies of early Connecticut Forestry Association publications, 1899-1905 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Includes copies of list of members and officers from annual reports for 1903-1905; and a copy of "A Bit of History".
  - Copies of historic publications, 1899-1942; 9 photocopies (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Includes copies of "Practical Forestry" (1939); "Publication no. 11" (1922); "Connecticut Needs Forests and Parks" (1927); "Fourth Annual Bulletin of the Connecticut Forestry Association" (1906); "A Bit of History" (1899); "Roadside Woodland Reservations" (1931); "Flood Control in Connecticut" (1936); "Bulletin" (1942); and "Connecticut Highway Shade Tree Conference Opens Way for Constructive Program" (1926).
  - Bell, Michael M. "Did New England Go Downhill?" Geographical Review 79, no. 4 New York: American Geographical Society of New York, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor 1946-1947. Public document number 97. Hartford: State of Connecticut (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Krug, E.C. and C. R. Frink. Effects of Acid Rain on Soil and Water. Bulletin 811. New Haven: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1983 November (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Buttrick, P.L. The Effect of Forest Fires on Trees and Reproduction in Southern New England. Reprinted from volume 10, number 2 Forestry Quarterly, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Hawley, Ralph C. and William Maughan. The Eli Whitney Forest A Demonstration of Forestry Practice. Bulletin number 27. New Haven: Yale University School of Forestry, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Explorer's Guide to Nature in Eastern Connecticut. Columbia, CT: Sierra Club, Connecticut Chapter, Northeast Group, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Digman, Dr. Ralph E. An Exposure of the Triassic Eastern Border Fault. Miscellaneous series number 2 reprinted from the American Journal on Science 248, number 1, pages 37-45. State Geological and Natural History Survey of Connecticut, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Extra important copies of early Connecticut Forestry Association publications, 1899-1905; 7 photocopies (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Includes four copies of the first page of "A Bit of History" (1899); and three copies of an annual report list of members for 1904-1905.
  - Doppel, Alfred A. Farm Forest Tree Planting. Bulletin number 96. Storrs, CT: Connecticut Agricultural College Extension Service, 1926 March (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Fire Warden Directory. Hartford: State Park and Forest Commission, Forestry Division, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Fishing for Values: A Primer for River Protection Activists in the use of Contingent Valuation as an Economic Tool for Conserving Anadromous Fisheries. Volume 1. Montpelier, VT: Northeast Natural Resource Center of the Natioanl Wildlife Federation and River Watch Network, 1995 June (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - State Board of Fisheries and Game, Lake and Pond Survey Unit. A Fishery Survey of Important Connecticut Lakes. Bulletin number 63. Public document number 47. Hartford: State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - 80th Anniversary Connecticut State Park and Forest Commission., 1963; 2 duplicate copies (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Connecticut Forest and Park Association., 1946 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Fifty-Fifth Annual Report of the Commissioners oF Public Parks. New Haven: City of New Haven, Department of Parks, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Flood Control Papers Presented at the Sixty-Second Annual Meeting of the American Forestry Association. Washington, D.C.: American Forestry Association, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Forest Lands of the United States, Report of the Joint Committee on Forestry, Congress of the United States, Pursuant to S. Con. Res. 31 (75th Congress) [and] H. Con. Res. 11, 23, and 51 (76th Congress). 77th Congress, 1st Session, document number 32. Washington, D.C.: United States Government Printing Office, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Smith, David M. The Forests of the United States., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Goodman, Robert B. Forest Management., 1927 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Goodman, Robert B. Forest Products Utilization in the National Economy., 1940; 2 duplicate copies (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Lunt, Herbert A. The Forest Soils of Connecticut. Bulletin number 523. New Haven: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1948 July (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Forest Trees of Connecticut A Pocket Manual. Hartford: Connecticut State Park and Forest Commission, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Forest Trees of Southern New England, 1955-1974, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Forest Trees Common to Southern New England and Adjacent Areas in New York State A Pocket Manual. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1955
    - Forest Trees of Southern New England. Hartford: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1965
    - Forest Trees of Southern New England. East Hartford: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1974
    - Forest Trees of Southern New England. Middletown: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, undated
  - Sudworth, George B. Check List of the Forest Trees of the United States Their Names and Ranges. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Division of Forestry, bulletin number 17. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1898 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The Forestry Primer. Washington, D.C.: American Tree Association, 1926; 2 duplicate copies (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Korstian, Clarence F. Forestry on Private Lands in the United States. Duke University School of Forestry bulletin 8. Durham, NC: Duke University, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Forests in Flood Control, Supplemental Report to the Committee on Flood Control, House of Representatives, Seventy-Fourth Congress, Second Session, on H.R. 12517 To Provide for a Permanent System of Flood Control and for Other Purposes. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1936; 3 duplicate copies (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Four Years Along Connecticut Highways. Hartford: State Highway Department, Bureau of Roadside Development, circa 1931 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Fourth Annual Bulletin of the Connecticut Forestry Association. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Frontiers of Plant Science. 22, no. 1 and 56, no. 1. New Haven: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1969, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Agar, William Macdonough. The Geology of the Shepaug Aqueduct Tunnel, Litchfield County, Connecticut. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Flint, Richard Foster. The Glacial Geology of Connecticut. State Geological and Natural History Survey bulletin number 47. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Greenways for Connecticut. A Report to the Governor from the Connecticut Greenways Committee Hartford: The Greenways Committee, 1994 December; 2 duplicate copies (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Guides to the Appalachian Trail, 1931-1938 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - The Connecticut Trail System "Follow the Blue Blazes". Appalachian Trail, South Portion. Publication number 19 F. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1931 October
    - The Connecticut Trail System "Follow the Blue Blazes". Appalachian Trail (South) and Mattatuck Trail (West). Publication number 19 H. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1931 November 1
    - The Connecticut Trail System "Follow the Blue Blazes". Appalachian Trail. Publication number 19 N. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1934 May
    - Guide to the Appalachian Trail in Maine. Publication number 4 (Third Edition). Washington, D.C.: The Appalachian Trail Conference, 1938
    - Guide to the Appalachian Trail in New England. Publication number 21. Boston: New England Trail Conference, 1933
  - Guide to Connecticut State Parks and Forests. Hartford: State Park and Forest Commission, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Rice, Wiliam North and Wilbur Garland Foye. Guide to the Geology of Middletown, Connecticut, and Vicinity. State Geological and Natural History Survey bulletin number 41. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Guide Book of the Long Trail Eleventh Edition. Rutland, VT: The Green Mountain Club, Inc., 1937 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - A Guide to Protecting Our Blue Trails., undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - 1936-1955 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
    - Hosley, N. W.. Bulletin number 19. Petersham, MA: Harvard Forest, 1936
    - Cline, A. C. and S. H. Spurr.. Bulletin number 21. Petersham, MA: Harvard Forest, 1942
    - Bess, Henry A., Stephen H. Spurr, and E. W. Littlefield.. Bulletin number 22. Petersham, MA: Harvard Forest, 1947
    - Stout, Benjamin B.. Bulletin number 24. Petersham, MA: Harvard Forest, 1952
    - Goodlett, John C.. Bulletin number 25. Petersham, MA: Harvard Forest, 1954
    - Barraclough, Solon L. and Ernest M. Gould, Jr.. Bulletin number 26. Petersham, MA: Harvard Forest, 1955
  - Hawes, Austin F. A Christmas Greeting, 1956-1962 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Hawes, Austin F. publications, 1908-1928 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report of the Forester. Part IV, forestry publication number 4, 1908
    - Forest Fires in Connecticut, 1910-1922 (inclusive). Hartford: State Forester, 1923
    - The Work of a Forest Protective Association. Hartford: State Forester, 1924
    - Fletcher, E. D. and Austin F. Hawes. The Use of Lumber and Wood in Connecticut, 1928
  - Hawes, Austin F. History of Forestry in Connecticut, Volume 1, 1849-1933, circa 1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Hawes, Austin F. History of Forestry in Connecticut, Volume 2, 1934-1944, circa 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
    1 typescript copy and 1 photocopy.
  - Hicock, Henry W. History of Forestry in Connecticut, circa 1949 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Altamura, Robert J. A History of the State Geological and Natural History Survey of Connecticut. Reprinted from The State Geological Surveys - A History. Hartford: Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection, Natural Resources Center, State Geological and Natural History Survey of Connecticut, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The Home Landscape. Storrs, CT: University of Connecticut, College of Agriculture Extension Service, 1962, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Warner, Benjamin A. How Barkhamsted Got Its Name: And Other Short Stories and Poems, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - How to Burn Wood. 6th ed. Bulletin number 28. New Haven: Northeastern Wood Utilization Council, 1949 June; 3 duplicate copies (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The Hunter in Conservation: A collection of studies and reports summarizing the role of the hunter in the American conservation movement. Newtown, CT: Council for Wildlife Conservation and Education, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore. Hunting Trips on the Prairie and in the Mountains, "Hunting Trips of a Ranchman", Part II. New York: G. P. Putnam's Sons, 1902 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Hawes, Austin F. Hurricane Damaged Forests Still An Important State Asset. Rockville, CT: T. F. Rady & Co., 1939; 2 duplicate copies (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Libby, George K. Jess Ramblin', circa 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Price, Overton W. The Land We Live In: The Boys' Book of Conservation. Boston: Small, Maynard and Company, 1911; 1 book (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Landscape and the Environment: Patterns for the Future. New London, CT: Program in Human Ecology, Connecticut College, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - The Legend of the Sleeping Giant. A Poem. New Haven, 1887 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Peirson, H. B.. Bulletin number 3. Petersham, MA: Harvard Forest, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Log Skidder Safety Manual for operators and mechanics. Chicago: Equipment Manufacturers Institute, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Logging and Water Quality in Connecticut: A Practical Guide for Protecting Water Quality while Harvesting Forest Products. East Hartford, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Moore, Fred Holmsley, M.A. Marbles and Limestones of Connecticut. Bulletin number 56. Public document number 47. Hartford: State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Merritt Parkway Number. Bridgeport: Fairfield County Planning Association, 1933 November (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Message of Governor Gifford Pinchot to the General Assembly of Pennsylvania. Delivered in Person to the Joint Session in the House of Representatives, 1927 January 4 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Connecticut Forest and Park Association publications, 1922-1957, undated (Box 18, Folder 18-20)
    - A Mile of Shade Tree to Commemorate George Washington Bicentennial, 1732-1932. Publication number 23. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1932 March; 2 duplicate copies
    - Cline, A. C. and H. J. MacAloney. Additional Notes on the Improvement of Weeviled White Pine Plantations. Publication number 24. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, undated; 2 duplicate copies
    - Better Roadsides. Publication number 41. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1940 January
    - The Connecticut Forest and Park Association and Its Work. Publication number 28. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, undated; 3 duplicate copies
    - Connecticut Woodland. Volume 1, no. 1. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1936 February
    - Do You Know Why Connecticut Needs State Forests? Publication number 25. Forestry puzzle number 1. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, undated; 2 duplicate copies
    - Editorial Endorsement of Work of Connecticut Forest and Park Association in Connection with Roadside Beautification, "Roadside Snapshots", Editorial from New Haven Register, 1930 August 31
    - The Farmer and Sportsman in Connecticut: A Cooperative Program of Wildlife Restoration. Hartford: Connecticut State Board of Fisheries and Game, 1934 November
    - A Forest, Park and Wild Life Conservation Program for Connecticut: Outline of Forestry and allied Legislation submitted to 1925 Session of Connecticut General Assembly. Publication number 14. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1925 January
    - Graves, Col. Henry S. Forestry and Rural Organization, 1922 May 27; 3 duplicate copies
    - How to Burn Wood: New Methods and New Markets. Publication numbers 33, 33a, and 33c-d. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1936-1942
    - How to Cut Wood with Less Labor. Publication number 43. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1942 October
    - Buttrick, P. L. and G. A. Cromie. The Organization of City Shade Tree Work. Reprinted from The American City Magazine, 1927 May
    - Remarks by Henry S. Graves at the Dedication of the Toumey Road in the Mohawk State Forest, Cromwall, Connecticut. Delivered at the Spring Field Meeting of the Connecticut Forest and Park Association. Publication number 29. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1935 June 15; 2 duplicate copies
    - Roadside Woodland Reservations. Publication number 20. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1931 May
    - Roadside Shade Trees: A Manual of Roadside Improvement for Tree Wardens and Others Interested. Publication number 18. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1928 January
    - Sherwood Island and what it means to -- Connecticut - Fairfield County - the Town of Westport. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1925 February
    - Supplement to the Connecticut Walk Book. Wallingford, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1957 August
    - Town Forests. Publication number 44. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1945 May
    - Buttrick, P. L. Town Forests and Parks for Connecticut. Publication number 15. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1925 December; 2 duplicate copies
    - Township Zoning. Publication number 37. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1938 April; 4 duplicate copies
    - Volunteers Needed in every Connecticut Town to Assist in the War on Dutch Elm Disease. Publication number 26. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1935 January; 3 duplicate copies
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets, circa 2005, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - The Community Investment Act: A Guide to Public Act 228, circa 2005
    - The Governor's Residence Conservancy, Restoring Connecticut's first house, undated
    - Hill-Stead Museum Trail Guide, undated
    - Lyman Orchards. A Country Tradition Since 1741. Middlefield, CT: Lyman Orchards, undated
  - Miscellaneous publications, 1932, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - The Principles and Policy for the Government and Control of the Connecticut State Parks, Approved by the Governor, May, 1918. Hartford: Connecticut State Park and Forest Commission, 1936 May 1
    - Tramping Trails in New England. Publication number 20. Pittsfield, MA: New England Trail Conference, 1932
  - Buttrick, P. L. Connecticut's State Flower the Mountain Laurel: A Forest Plant. Publication number 1. New Haven: Marsh Botanical Garden of Yale University, 1924; 2 duplicate copies (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Taylor, Sally L., Glenn D. Dreyer, and William A. Niering. Native Shrubs for Landscaping. Bulletin number 30. New London, CT: The Connecticut Arboretum at Connecticut College, 1987 September (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - New England Trail Conference, 1921-1932 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Pray, James Sturgis. Beauty in Trails: An Address Before the New England Trail Conference, January 19, 1923. Publication number 9. Boston: New England Trail Conference
    - Comey, Arthur C. Going Light. Publication number 11. Boston: New England Trail Conference, 1924
    - Comey, Arthur C. Going Light. 2nd edition. Publication number 11. Boston: New England Trail Conference, 1932
    - Howard, William G. Open Camps. Publication number 7. Boston: New England Trail Conference, 1922
    - Comey, Arthur C. and Paul R. Jenks. Sign Painting. Publication number 8. Boston: New England Trail Conference, 1923
    - Goodrich, Nathaniel L., et al. Standards of Trail Construction and Maintenance, Logging Road Trails, the Naming of Trails, [and] Trail Signs. Publication number 6. Boston: New England Trail Conference, 1921
    - Backus, Dana C. The Summer Camp on the Trail. Publication number 18. New Haven: New England Trail Conference, 1931
    - Goodrich, N. L. Trail Location: A Paper Delivered before New England Trail Conference, January 23, 1925. Publication number 14. Boston: New England Trail Conference, 1926
  - Northeastern Wood Utilization Council bulletins, 1946-1952 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Connwood Incorporated: An Experiment in Cooperative Marketing. Bulletin number 34. New Haven: Northeastern Wood Utilization Council, Inc., 1951 April
    - Extractives from Northeastern Woods. Bulletin number 9. New Haven: Northeastern Wood Utilization Council, 1946 August
    - Marketing Sawdust and Chipped Wood. Bulletin number 38. New Haven: Northeastern Wood Utilization Council, Inc., 1952 March
    - New Developments in Hardwood Pulp. Bulletin number 14. New Haven: Northeastern Wood Utilization Council, 1947 January
    - The Pulping of Southern New England Hardwoods. Bulletin number 20. New Haven: Northeastern Wood Utilization Council, 1948 June
    - Tannin from Waste Bark. Bulletin number 39. New Haven: Northeastern Wood Utilization Council, Inc., 1952 September
  - Stewart, Lincoln, M. A. The Petrology of the Prospect Porphyritic Gneiss of Connecticut. Bulletin number 55. Hartford: State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Bishop, James S. Pheasant Mortality and Nesting Success. Canton Center Study Area, January, 1941 through June, 1942. Report of Pittman-Robertson Project 3-R. Pittman-Robertson bulletin number 1. Hartford: Connecticut Board of Fisheries and Game, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pinchot publications, 1900-1914 (Box 18, Folder 29-31)
    - Pinchot, Gifford. A Primer of Forestry. Part I - The Forest. Bulletin number 24. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1900; 1 book
    - Pinchot, Gifford. A Primer of Forestry. Part II - Practical Forestry. Bulletin number 24, part II. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1905; 1 book
    - Pinchot, Gifford. The Training of a Forester. Philadelphia: J. B. Lippincott Company, 1914; 1 book
    - Pinchot, Gifford. The Training of a Forester. Philadelphia: J. B. Lippincott Company, 1914; 1 book
      Included with the book are 2 pages (front and back) from Helen Cody Wetmore's Last of the Great Scouts: The Life Story of William F. Cody.
  - Plan of Work for Conducting the Connecticut Forest Resource Plan. East Hartford, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1982; 3 duplicate copies (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Prepared under contract with the Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection.
  - Plant Life. Storrs, CT: Cooperative Extension Service, College of Agriculture, University of Connecticut, circa 1965 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Pinchot, Gifford. The Power Monopoly: Its Make-Up and Its Menace, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - A Practical Guide for Protecting Water Quality while Harvesting Forest Products. Connecticut RC&D Forestry Committee, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hawes, Austin F. The Present Condition of Connecticut Forests, A Neglected Resource. Hartford: State Forester, 1933; 2 duplicate copies (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Small, Stephen J. Preserving Family Lands: A Landowner's Introduction to Tax Issues and Other Considerations. Boston: Powers & Hall Professional Corporation, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the American Forestry Congress at its Sessions Held at Cincinnnati, Ohio, in April, 1882, and at Montreal, Canada, in August, 1882. Washington: American Forestry Congress, 1883 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings of the Connecticut Forestry Association. Publication numbers 5, 6, and 8. Hartford: Hartford Printing Co., 1907-1914; 2 duplicate copies of publication number 6 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Project Learning Tree publications, 1998-2007 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Exploring Environmental Issues: Focus on Risk. Washington, D.C.: American Forest Foundation, 1998
    - John R. Camp Outdoor Classroom and Demonstration Forest. Project Learning Tree Loop Trail Educator Guidebook. Rockfall, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 2000